# PAMALE ALEXIS ANGE DAULI

A Frontend web developer motivated to get better in software industry by constantly learning using the power of internet through the online resources. I can build Responsive Websites using CSS and HTML and some JS. Also using content management system (CMD) like WordPress.

I am also an Angular novice developer and I possess a good understanding of Bootstrap. With more than 4 years of Internet Café as manager.

# Key Skills

Angular : Entry level
Typescript : Entry level
JavaScript : Proficient
NodeJS : Entry level
JSON : Proficient

HTML/HTML5 : Proficient (Many projects has been developed)CSS/CSS3 : Proficient (Many projects has been developed)

Bootstrap : Entry level
WordPress : Proficient
Firebase : Entry Level
Git & Github : Entry level

C language : Basic knowledge

Computer Literacy: MS Word, MS Excel, PowerPoint

Graphic Design : Basic knowledge of Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator

# **Projects**

1. Mini-Netflix Application

https://dauli-netflix.firebaseapp.com

Build with Angular

2. Portfolio Website 1

https://dauli.github.io/Portfolio

Technology used : CSS & CSS3, HTML5, Flexbox Media Queries, JavaScript,

& jQuery. And Responsive Design across different devices.

3. Portfolio Website 2

https://dauli.github.io/Portfolio-FCC

Technology used : HTML, HTML5, CSS, CSS3, Media Query, flexbox

Responsive Design across different devices.

4. Ecommerce Website

https://www.daulishop.com

Technology used: WordPress with Elementor page Builder

# **API Integration Projects**

5. Weather Application

https://dauli.github.io/weatherApp

Technology used : HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API Integration

6. Wikipedia View Page

https://codepen.io/alexisAnge/full/aYLNgx

Technology used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, WIKI API Integration Note: Build on **codepen**, it's not a responsive design.

7. Sandbox app

https://dauli.github.io/sandBox

Technology used: Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JSON, FetchApi

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Marlborough Holliday Apartments (Durban) - Receptionist - 07/2019 - Present

- Welcoming and informing customers
- Booking customers for holiday
- Receiving online bookings, register and distribute customers accordingly
- Attending phone calls
- Arranging, sorting and distribute couriers
- Distributing daily tasks to the cleaners

**Reference**: On request

#### Jenny Internet Café (Durban)

- **General Manager** - 05/2015 - 06/2018

- Doing online Applications for clients
- Typing of different kind of documents especially student assignments
- Scanning Documents by respecting different file format
- Emailing documents accordingly
- Maintaining computers by updating software and some virus remove
- Installing Operating Systems and applications on customer's computer.

Reference: On request

#### **EDUCATION**

1. PLURALSIGHT (Sponsored by Google and Andela) - Remote

Mobile Web (JS & Angular )

05/2019 - /01/2020

2. FreeCodeCamp - Remote

Responsive Web Design

02/2018 – 11/2018

3. UDACITY (Sponsored by Google and Andela) - Remote

Google Africa Front-End Web

05/2018 – 09/2018